<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[RSS Feed]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Marketing Executive Account Developer at the Institute of Physics Publishing]]></description>
        <link>https://barbarazarzycka.com</link>
        <image>
            <url>https://barbarazarzycka.com/logo.jpg</url>
            <title>RSS Feed</title>
            <link>https://barbarazarzycka.com</link>
        </image>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 05:12:09 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://barbarazarzycka.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 05:12:09 GMT</pubDate>
        <copyright><![CDATA[All rights reserved 2023]]></copyright>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[“Ikigai” book review]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[I picked this book as I needed something short to read for a couple of hours’ flight. The book draws a meaningful life picture and teaches about a long, happy life.]]></description>
            <link>https://barbarazarzycka.com/ikigai-book-review</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://barbarazarzycka.com/ikigai-book-review</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to choose an undergraduate dissertation topic]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Congratulations! Thinking about the dissertation topic and where to start means you made it through most of the university and are in your final year! Over a year ago, I was in the same position and felt overwhelmed. So, here I am now to help you a little!]]></description>
            <link>https://barbarazarzycka.com/how-to-choose-an-undergraduate-dissertation-topic</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://barbarazarzycka.com/how-to-choose-an-undergraduate-dissertation-topic</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[“How not to die” book review]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Did you realise how the world has accelerated in recent years, and then suddenly everything changed? The pandemic forced us to slow down, step back and look at our lives.]]></description>
            <link>https://barbarazarzycka.com/how-not-to-die-book-review</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://barbarazarzycka.com/how-not-to-die-book-review</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Review of one-year work experience at the multinational corporation]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[My one-year journey in the company from my dream automotive industry almost ended. I will hand over projects to the next placement student during the next two weeks. Time to review!]]></description>
            <link>https://barbarazarzycka.com/work-experience-review-at-the-multinational-corporation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://barbarazarzycka.com/work-experience-review-at-the-multinational-corporation</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One thing everyone must know about sustainability]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[I will never forget what I have heard from one of the most popular now documentary movies. Of course, the topic is not new, but it is shocking.
There is big hype now on the Seaspiracy movie, and I don't say everyone should watch it as it is intense for highly sensitive people.]]></description>
            <link>https://barbarazarzycka.com/one-thing-everyone-must-know-about-sustainability</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://barbarazarzycka.com/one-thing-everyone-must-know-about-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The brain also needs a warm-up]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[How often did you expect your brain to start processing information and making a great outcome in a written work or any other form immediately? I am sure you have been there at least once. Interestingly, the brain, like every other muscle, needs a warm-up. It is slightly different from the one you do before the exercises.]]></description>
            <link>https://barbarazarzycka.com/the-brain-also-needs-a-warm-up</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://barbarazarzycka.com/the-brain-also-needs-a-warm-up</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[“The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People” book review]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This book is pleasant to read or listen to, and it’s full of sometimes such evident life principles and practices that are needed to be reminded of. The book was first published over thirty years ago, yet the content is universal and may help change your perception and life today.]]></description>
            <link>https://barbarazarzycka.com/the-7-habits-of-highly-effective-people-book-review</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://barbarazarzycka.com/the-7-habits-of-highly-effective-people-book-review</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to make lockdown suck less Vol. 2]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[How did you spend your free time during the lockdown? This question may come up in a future interview, and it may be helpful to have a good answer. We all deal differently with the pandemic and have different personal circumstances that may affect how we spend our free time. Whatever your situation, showing what you have learned in this challenging time will be good.]]></description>
            <link>https://barbarazarzycka.com/how-to-make-lockdown-suck-less-vol-2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://barbarazarzycka.com/how-to-make-lockdown-suck-less-vol-2</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rising culture of remote work — a literature review]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Is anyone interested in applying for a business-related course at the university? Then, be prepared to read and write a lot. (...) Here are my research tips and findings on the topic.]]></description>
            <link>https://barbarazarzycka.com/rising-culture-of-remote-work-a-literature-review</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://barbarazarzycka.com/rising-culture-of-remote-work-a-literature-review</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2021 January review]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[No one wished for 2021 to start with another lockdown. If you are an extrovert like me, we are in the same boat, struggling with minimal social contact, which usually keeps us up and running. Introverts, you lucky bastards. I hope you are making the most of this time.]]></description>
            <link>https://barbarazarzycka.com/2021-january-review</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://barbarazarzycka.com/2021-january-review</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to make lockdown suck less — “We need to talk about love” book review]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This book isn't one of these cheesy books about romance and unicorns you would like to read about. "We need to talk about love" is an excellent piece of science cut into 365 pages of delightful, full of based on true stories, fourteen chapters.]]></description>
            <link>https://barbarazarzycka.com/how-to-make-lockdown-suck-less-we-need-to-talk-about-love-book-review</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://barbarazarzycka.com/how-to-make-lockdown-suck-less-we-need-to-talk-about-love-book-review</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Social media — bring the focus back on track]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Are you feeling tired and unmotivated all of the time? Did you wonder why it might be happening? Don’t you think you are focusing on too many things simultaneously and not giving enough attention to your tasks? ]]></description>
            <link>https://barbarazarzycka.com/social-media-bring-the-focus-back-on-track</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://barbarazarzycka.com/social-media-bring-the-focus-back-on-track</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Work from home during pandemic & Placement Year]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[In April 2020, I got a job offer from a global company in the automotive industry. A dream come true, I thought. And then everything changed a couple of months into lockdown and the pandemic. ]]></description>
            <link>https://barbarazarzycka.com/work-from-home-during-pandemic-and-placement-year</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://barbarazarzycka.com/work-from-home-during-pandemic-and-placement-year</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Undergraduate study 2021 / COVID-19]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Online learning is stressful, and not having an opportunity to meet your coursemates and hang out with them is simply unfair – considering time spent at university the best time of your life.]]></description>
            <link>https://barbarazarzycka.com/undergraduate-study-2021-covid-19</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://barbarazarzycka.com/undergraduate-study-2021-covid-19</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[First Post]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Good Morning,

Isn’t the end of the year the best time to start something new? Of course, it is! Therefore, I’m writing today my very first post ever.]]></description>
            <link>https://barbarazarzycka.com/first-post</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://barbarazarzycka.com/first-post</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>